You walk past the same
vegetable every week at the
grocery store. It's a dollar
fifty a head, and it's
doing what a forty dollar
probiotic can't. The gut food
you've been ignoring costs a
dollar fifty. Cabbage is packed
with insoluble fiber, the kind
that moves things through your
gut and feeds your bacteria.
One cup cooked, that's four
grams of fiber, barely any
calories, and almost zero prep
time. Roast it with olive
oil and it caramelizes, gets
almost sweet, or ferment it
into sauerkraut. Now you've got
fiber and live bacteria in
one bite. If you're spending
twelve dollars on kombucha, the
cheapest thing in produce might
be doing the same job.
Three recipes, one ingredient, all
under twenty minutes. Recipes at
dailylifehacks.com. Free
every week.